(Amy:)I told her what a good guy you are,
(Amy:)but she thought it was a bad sign
(Amy:)that you didn't write
to her yourself.
(Amy:)She thought it made you seem
too shy and passive.
(Raj:)I'm not too shy and passive.
(Raj:)You write her back
and tell her I said that.
(Leonard:)You know,
when you have a second.
(Amy:)Look, I'll see if I can change
her mind tomorrow night.
(Raj:)What's happening tomorrow night?
(Amy:)I'm meeting her for coffee.
(Raj:)What?
(Amy:)We emailed back and forth a bit,
and we kind of hit it off.
(Raj:)I find a girl I like,
and you're stealing her?
(Amy:)No. We just ended up
having a lot in common.
(Amy:)We went to Harvard,
we like Chaucer,
were both hardcore into quilting.
(Raj:)Your words fall like acid rain
on the wounded petals of my heart.
(Howard:)That's Sheldon.
He says he'll be down in a minute.
(Bernadette:)-What are you doing?
(Howard:)He's not coming out
until he sees proof
(Howard:)you don't have an air freshener
in your car.